=Deity of Love= =Episode 16=
= إله الحب = = الحلقة 16 =
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Xiaoqing.
شياو تشينغ.
Don't go there.
لا تذهب هناك.
She's a demon.
إنها شيطان.
She killed Wanying.
قتلت وانينج.
Xiaoqing
شياو تشينغ
is a demon.
هو شيطان.
Ning Yu,
نينغ يو
what are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Kill this demon.
اقتل هذا الشيطان.
It must have nothing to do with Xiaoqing.
يجب ألا يكون لها علاقة بشياو تشينغ.
It must.
يجب.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
All demons should be killed.
يجب قتل كل الشياطين.
If she doesn't kill people today,
إذا لم تقتل الناس اليوم ،
she will kill people tomorrow.
ستقتل الناس غدا.
I didn't kill anyone.
أنا لم أقتل أحدا.
We have been together for so long.
لقد كنا معا لفترة طويلة.
Don't you know her?
الا تعرفها
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
The demon is a demon.
الشيطان شيطان.
There's no difference.
ليس هناك فرق.
Kill this demon.
اقتل هذا الشيطان.
Kill her.
أقتلها.
Ning Yu.
نينغ يو.
Listen to Brother Xiuning
استمع إلى الأخ Xiuning
and put down your sword.
وانزل سيفك.
Ning Yu.
نينغ يو.
Put down your sword.
ضع سيفك جانبا.
You are a demon hunter.
أنت صياد الشياطين.
Why do you insist on protecting a demon?
لماذا تصر على حماية الشيطان؟
Even if I'm a monster,
حتى لو كنت وحشًا ،
I should go to hell?
يجب أن أذهب إلى الجحيم؟
Get out of my way.
ابتعد عن طريقي.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Then you will get your own way.
ثم ستحصل على طريقتك الخاصة.
Xiaoqing.
شياو تشينغ.
Ning Yu.
نينغ يو.
Are you here to capture me?
هل انت هنا لتأسرني؟
Xiaoqing.
شياو تشينغ.
You're a demon hunter, while I'm a demon.
أنت صياد شيطان بينما أنا شيطان.
People and demons can never live in harmony.
لا يمكن للناس والشياطين أن يعيشوا في وئام.
Can you really accept that I'm a demon?
هل يمكنك حقًا قبول أنني شيطان؟
You demon,
أنت شيطان ،
how dare you break into the Soul Department?
كيف تجرؤ على اقتحام قسم الروح؟
How is it going?
كيف الحال أو كيف تسير الأمور؟
My lord,
ربي،
there was some accident.
كان هناك بعض الحوادث.
I was nearly found.
تم العثور علي تقريبا.
What a good-for-nothing you are!
ما هو جيد مقابل لا شيء أنت!
Sister Xi Ling,
الأخت شي لينغ ،
why do you come in the palace without any permission?
لماذا تدخل القصر بدون اذن؟
Department Head, please forgive me.
رئيس القسم ، أرجوك سامحني.
I just saw
لقد رايت للتو
a demon sneak in.
شيطان يتسلل.
I'm here to have a check.
أنا هنا لإجراء فحص.
Oh?
أوه؟
Demon?
شيطان؟
Demons can be found anywhere in the world,
يمكن العثور على الشياطين في أي مكان في العالم ،
except the Soul Department.
باستثناء قسم الروح.
But I did see it.
لكني رأيت ذلك.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Are you suspecting me?
هل تشك بي؟
I dare not.
لا أجرؤ.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
Do what you should do.
افعل ما يجب عليك فعله
Don't forget
لا تنسى
how the Snake Demon ran.
كيف ركض شيطان الأفعى.
Yeah.
نعم.
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
I'm leaving now.
انا راحل الان.
Why...
لماذا...
Why is Xiaoqing a demon?
لماذا شياو تشينغ شيطان؟
Brother Xiuning.
الأخ Xiuning.
Can you stop being like that?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن أن تكون هكذا؟
Will demons definitely kill people?
هل ستقتل الشياطين الناس بالتأكيد؟
Don't forget,
لا تنسى،
demons will definitely do evil things.
سوف تفعل الشياطين بالتأكيد أشياء شريرة.
Can't people do those too?
ألا يستطيع الناس فعل ذلك أيضًا؟
But is't it
لكن أليس كذلك
what the Soul Department has said?
ماذا قال قسم الروح؟
The Soul Department.
قسم الروح.
Even if Xiaoqing is a demon,
حتى لو كان شياو تشينغ شيطانًا ،
I also believe that
أنا أيضا أؤمن بذلك
she won't kill anyone.
لن تقتل أحدا.
How do you prove it?
كيف تثبت ذلك؟
I will prove Xiaoqing's innocence,
سأثبت براءة شياو تشينغ
as well as the existence of good demons.
وكذلك وجود الشياطين الصالحة.
I will find out the truth
سأكتشف الحقيقة
to clear Xiaoqing's name.
لمسح اسم شياو تشينغ.
Xiaoqing, wait for me.
شياو تشينغ ، انتظرني.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(حق إعادة بث المسرحية على الإنترنت ملك لي.) (شركة Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co.، Ltd.)